Monday, November 18 2024

Breaking News

* [If You Think Kamala Harris Was Serious About The Things She Promised During The Recent Presidential Campaign, You’re Dead Wrong](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/if-you-think-kamala-harris-was-serious-about-the-things-she-promised-during-the-recent-presidential-campaign-youre-dead-wrong/)
* [Jen Psaki Admits Dems Are ‘In The Wilderness’ Without A ‘Clear Leader Of The Party’](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/jen-psaki-admits-dems-are-in-the-wilderness-without-a-clear-leader-of-the-party/)
* [Now an Excellent Time to Add 4 more Justices of the Supreme Court](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/now-an-excellent-time-to-add-4-more-justices-of-the-supreme-court/)
* [Trump Confirms He Will Declare National Emergency, Use Military Assets For Mass Deportation](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-confirms-he-will-declare-national-emergency-use-military-assets-for-mass-deportation/)
* [Baseless Assaults Will Fill The Airwaves Until Nominations Complete](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/baseless-assaults-will-fill-the-airwaves-until-nominations-complete/)
* [Trump Sends His Clearest Message Yet To DOJ Bureaucrats With Unexpected Leadership Picks](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-sends-his-clearest-message-yet-to-doj-bureaucrats-with-unexpected-leadership-picks/)

*  Search for

[Home](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/)_/_Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

At [ConservativeDailyNews.com](https://conservativedailynews.com/ "Conservative Daily News") (CDN), we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Below is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit _ConservativeDailyNews.com_, and how we safeguard your information. We will **never** sell your personal information to third parties.

**Names and Email Addresses:**

We will only collect email addresses and names when accounts are created on the site, or a user signs up for our email newsletter. This information is used solely to deliver requested notifications and/or emails. This information will NEVER be sold to a third party or used for any other purposes than those elected by the user.

**Data Deletion/Erasure**

At any time, if you would like to have all data that CDN may have collected to be permanently deleted you may send a request to webmaster@conservativedailynews.com to have your account deleted. Account deletion will completely remove any and all information related to your account from our website, servers, and third-party services.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used by us to create a better user experience and a secure experience.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on ConservativeDailyNews.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart\_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### Third Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://networkadvertising.org/).

### [How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/)

Support Conservative Daily News with a small donation via [Paypal or credit card](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/support-conservative-news/) that will go towards supporting the news and commentary you've come to appreciate.

Support CDN!

Your donations help us purchase content, pay for servers, and reduce advertising. We are currently fundraising for December. [CLICK HERE](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/privacy-policy/support-conservative-news) to help out or to see what we do with the money.  
**Current Fundraising for December:**

Created using the Donation Thermometer plugin https://wordpress.org/plugins/donation-thermometer/.41%

Red = Recurring Donations  
Orange = One-Time Donations

    [Trump Puts Bureaucrats Behind America’s Bungled Education System On Notice](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-puts-bureaucrats-behind-americas-bungled-education-system-on-notice/)
    
    November 16, 2024

    [Trump’s Sec Def Pick Will Give Pentagon Its First Real Wake Up Call In Decades](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trumps-sec-def-pick-will-give-pentagon-its-first-real-wake-up-call-in-decades/)
    
    November 14, 2024

Recent Posts

    [If You Think Kamala Harris Was Serious About The Things She Promised During The Recent Presidential Campaign, You’re Dead Wrong](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/if-you-think-kamala-harris-was-serious-about-the-things-she-promised-during-the-recent-presidential-campaign-youre-dead-wrong/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    [Jen Psaki Admits Dems Are ‘In The Wilderness’ Without A ‘Clear Leader Of The Party’](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/jen-psaki-admits-dems-are-in-the-wilderness-without-a-clear-leader-of-the-party/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    [Now an Excellent Time to Add 4 more Justices of the Supreme Court](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/now-an-excellent-time-to-add-4-more-justices-of-the-supreme-court/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    [Biden Caves, Allows Ukraine To Use US Missiles For Long-Range Strikes Inside Russia](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/biden-caves-allows-ukraine-to-use-us-missiles-for-long-range-strikes-inside-russia/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    [Trump Confirms He Will Declare National Emergency, Use Military Assets For Mass Deportation](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-confirms-he-will-declare-national-emergency-use-military-assets-for-mass-deportation/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    [Baseless Assaults Will Fill The Airwaves Until Nominations Complete](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/baseless-assaults-will-fill-the-airwaves-until-nominations-complete/)
    
    November 18, 2024

    November 18, 2024

    November 18, 2024

* [Gun Control Groups Fail to See Difference in Charitable Fundraising with Firearms and Criminal Use of Firearms](https://www.thegunpage.com/gun-control-groups-fail-to-see-difference-in-charitable-fundraising-with-firearms-and-criminal-use-of-firearms/10611957)
* [Memphis City Leaders Just Keep Pushing Their Anti-Gun Schemes](https://www.thegunpage.com/memphis-city-leaders-just-keep-pushing-their-anti-gun-schemes/10611950)
* [Collegiate Rifle: Akron Just Misses The Mark In Weekend Trifecta Against Navy, Nebraska](https://www.thegunpage.com/collegiate-rifle-akron-just-misses-the-mark-in-weekend-trifecta-against-navy-nebraska/10611956)
* [Pennsylvania District Attorney Suing To Allow Medical Marijuana Users Firearms Access](https://www.thegunpage.com/pennsylvania-district-attorney-suing-to-allow-medical-marijuana-users-firearms-access/10611948)
* [Team Savage’s Matt Alwine Wins Production Division Title At 2024 PRS Finale](https://www.thegunpage.com/team-savages-matt-alwine-wins-production-division-title-at-2024-prs-finale/10611952)
* [Achieve Next-Level Training with the Strikeman X SIRT Dry-Fire Laser Training Pistol](https://www.thegunpage.com/achieve-next-level-training-with-the-strikeman-x-sirt-dry-fire-laser-training-pistol/10611940)

Follow Us on Social Media

Links We Love

Contact Us

© Copyright 2008-2024, All Rights Reserved  |  [Bald Eagle Media, LLC](https://baldeaglehq.com/)

Recent Comments

* Stanley Warner on [Five Government Programs That Musk’s Government Efficiency Agency Could Put On The Chopping Block](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/five-government-programs-that-musks-government-efficiency-agency-could-put-on-the-chopping-block/#comment-783286)
* Stanley Warner on [Trump Sends His Clearest Message Yet To DOJ Bureaucrats With Unexpected Leadership Picks](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-sends-his-clearest-message-yet-to-doj-bureaucrats-with-unexpected-leadership-picks/#comment-783285)
* Beverly Sellers on [The Voters Have Made Their Decision: The Real Evil In American Politics is…The Democrats](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/the-voters-have-made-their-decision-the-real-evil-in-american-politics-is-the-democrats/#comment-783274)
* Stanley Warner on [Trump Puts Bureaucrats Behind America’s Bungled Education System On Notice](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/trump-puts-bureaucrats-behind-americas-bungled-education-system-on-notice/#comment-783269)
* Stanley Warner on [Can A FOX Weekend Host Run Our Military? Absolutely](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/can-a-fox-weekend-host-run-our-military-absolutely/#comment-783268)
* Stanley Warner on [The Voters Have Made Their Decision: The Real Evil In American Politics is…The Democrats](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/the-voters-have-made-their-decision-the-real-evil-in-american-politics-is-the-democrats/#comment-783267)
* Ted Thomas on [The Voters Have Made Their Decision: The Real Evil In American Politics is…The Democrats](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/the-voters-have-made-their-decision-the-real-evil-in-american-politics-is-the-democrats/#comment-783266)
* Stanley Warner on [May God Bless Donald Trump And His Presidency](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/may-god-bless-donald-trump-and-his-presidency/#comment-783259)
* Stanley Warner on [A Lesson For Democrats — Don’t Be Weird](https://www.conservativedailynews.com/2024/11/a-lesson-for-democrats-dont-be-weird/#comment-783258)

Log In

 Remember me Log In
